

AQUINO TEGAR

+62 852 9142 4319 aquinotgr@pm.me

PROFILE

An early experienced and highly motivated person who personally love challenges and problem solving also insecure about his digital life.

Experienced using Laravel, docker and bootstrap for 1+ years, into open source, currently learn to build an iOS app. I love rhymes and catchy beat.

INTERESTS

Techy stuff
Minimalism
Open Source
Hip - Hop
Apple ecosystem
Al

SKILLS

PHP	••••
Laravel	••••
Javascript	••••
HTML CSS	••••
MySQL	• • • • •
Swift 4	••••
Python	• • • • •
Linux	••••

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Indotech Group, Aug 2015 - Jul 2017

- Develop Web company web app using Laravel.
- Manage and Design company profile website using Worpdress.
- Manage Company Database.
- Provide server and local development.
- Provide general IT Support.

WEB CO-DEVELOPER

PT Desnet, Jan 2014 - Mar 2014

- Assist the web developer using Wordpress.
- · Manage company database.
- Entry a bunch of data.

EDUCATION

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

Amikom University, 2017 - Present

COMPUTER SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

SMK Telekomunikasi Tunas Harapan 2012 - 2015



github.com/aquinotgr00



twitter.com/aquinotgr00



linkedin.com/in/aquino-tegar-a8166a142/